{
    "subject": "resource/Steven_G._Vandenberg",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Steven Vandenberg (born July 15, 1915, Den Helder, The Netherlands d. August 27, 1992, Boulder, Colorado, United States) was a behavior geneticist who immigrated to the US after the Second World War, obtaining his Ph.D. from the University of Michigan in 1955.From 1960 to 1967 he worked at the University of Louisville School of Medicine as director of the Louisville Twin Study. In 1970 he moved to the Institute of Behavior Genetics at the University of Colorado at Boulder, where he remained until his retirement. Vandenberg received many honors and awards during his lifetime, including being the first recipient of the Behavior Genetics Association's Dobzhansky Career Award in 1977. Vandenberg served as President of the Behavior Genetics Association (1984\u20131985) and was the founding editor-in-chief of their scientific journal Behavior Genetics.",
    "human_readable": "Steven Vandenberg was a behavior geneticist who immigrated to the US after the Second World War, obtaining his Ph.D. from the University of Michigan in 1955.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9402112364768982,
            "question": "Where did Steven Vandenberg immigrate to after World War II?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8813542127609253,
            "question": "From which university did Steven Vandenberg obtain his Ph.D.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.860691487789154,
            "question": "When did Steven Vandenberg immigrate to the US?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7961454391479492,
            "question": "What event prompted Steven Vandenberg's immigration to the US?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7319006323814392,
            "question": "What year did Steven Vandenberg receive his Ph.D.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6259231567382812,
            "question": "What is a behavior geneticist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38257721066474915,
            "question": "Besides the US, where else did Steven Vandenberg likely live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3625045120716095,
            "question": "Can you describe the potential impact of Steven Vandenberg's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34798839688301086,
            "question": "What was Steven Vandenberg's field of study?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30383655428886414,
            "question": "What type of research might Steven Vandenberg have conducted?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Steven Vandenberg was a behavior geneticist who immigrated to the US after the Second World War, obtaining his Ph.D. from the University of Michigan in 1955.",
            "html": "dbpedia_60_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Steven Vandenberg's field of study?",
            "html": "dbpedia_60_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the potential impact of Steven Vandenberg's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_60_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides the US, where else did Steven Vandenberg likely live?",
            "html": "dbpedia_60_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_60_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_60_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_60_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_60_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_60_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_60_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_60_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_60_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_60_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_60_65.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information and without prior knowledge, I can conclude that:\n\n* The triple \"Steven Vandenberg was a behavior geneticist who immigrated to the US after the Second World War, obtaining his Ph.D. from the University of Michigan in 1955\" is supported by the documents.\n\nHere's my response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided context supports that Steven Vandenberg was indeed a behavior geneticist who immigrated to the United States after the Second World War and obtained his Ph.D. from the University of Michigan in 1955."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}